You need to know who you are.
I am a spirit; you are a spirit living in a physical body, learning to live in the natural world.
I listen to my spirit because it is controlled by the Holy Spirit
for I walk not after the flesh but after the spirit.
I examine my leading in the light of God's Word.
So, you must know who you are.
Open your lips and confess this with me.
I am a spirit living in a physical body,
learning to live in the natural world.
I listen to the voice of my spirit because it is controlled by the Holy Spirit
for I walk not after the flesh but after the spirit.
I examine my leading in the light of God's Word, in Jesus' name.
Viewers all over the world, I know you are there.
You are a spirit; we only live in the physical body.
With God, all things are possible.
In Jesus Chist's name, we pray.
Whatever way you have been imprisoned by demons and evil spirits,
right now, you are declared free, in the name of Jesus!
You are released, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips: Whatever way you have been caged and imprisoned financially, health-wise,
physically and spiritually, right now, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, open your lips and begin to release yourself.
Viewers all over the world, I command that affliction, out!
Out of your body - that sickness, disease!
Command them out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, wherever you are right now, I say to the sickness and disease, leave my people!
In the name of Jesus, leave my people!
Wherever it is located, in your blood, bones, tendons,
you sickness, disease and affliction, leave my people!
You are declared free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name